moxsie.com 2009-02-21

# Privacy Policy

Product request submitted.

This privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") covers the website [shop.moxsie.com](http://shop.moxsie.com/ "shop.moxsie.com"), owned and operated by Moxsie, Inc. ("Moxsie", "we", "us", "our"). Moxsie knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Moxsie website, submitting information or using any of our products or services, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. You are also consenting to have your data transferred to and processed in the United States.

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**  
This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personal information that we gather when you are on the Moxsie website and when you use Moxsie services. The types of personal information collected include your name, your address, your e-mail address, your telephone number, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Moxsie's treatment of any personal information that Moxsie's business partners share with Moxsie. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Moxsie does not own or control, or to individuals that Moxsie does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information About Users Does Moxsie Collect?**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to personalize and improve our service. We collect the following types of information from our users:

A) Information You Provide to Us:

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials, sales offers and new products.

Registration: In order for you to use our website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your first and last name, your email address, your password, your country, your city and confirmation that you are 13 years or older and that you agree to the terms and conditions of Moxsie.com. When you use Moxsie, you may set up your profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, set up events, make want and have lists, post finds, comment and transmit information through various channels. In most cases, we retain it so that you can return to view saved lists or sent messages. When you update your information, we usually keep a back-up copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time. We collect this information in order to provide you the service and offer you a more personalized and relevant experience on Moxsie. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

B) Automatic Information:

• We may receive and store use information whenever you interact with us. Moxsie may automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your browser type, IP address, Moxsie cookie information, and the page you requested. Moxsie uses this traffic data, among other things, to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the website.

• Generally, our service may automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website and its components. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the website, so we can make the website appealing to as many users as possible. In addition, we may provide statistical information to our partners about how our users collectively use our website. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their areas and our website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal Web experience.

• We may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like an item, a store, or a brand and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you with a more relevant and personalized experience on Moxsie. We believe this benefits you

• We may also use information about you that we collect when you use our tools on other websites.

• Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Moxsie will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

C) E-mail Communications:

•We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Moxsie if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out emails with news or promotions. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at [unsubscribe@moxsie.com](mailto:unsubscribe@moxsie.com) and include sufficient information for us to identify your account.

•If you choose to use our information service to tell a contact about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your contact's email address. We will automatically send your contact a one-time email or instant message inviting him, her or them to visit the site. Moxsie stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a contact connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your contact may contact us at [support@moxsie.com](mailto:support@moxsie.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

D) Information from Other Sources:

For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**What about Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. We store certain information from your browser using cookies. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Moxsie. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Moxsie's most attractive features.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Will Moxsie Share My Mailing Lists or Address Book Information with Third Parties?**

We understand that businesses on Moxsie — such as brands, stores, or other Moxsie business partners — have customer email lists that they consider proprietary. Moxsie respects the confidential nature of these email lists and does not rent or sell this information to anyone. Moxsie asks you to invite your friends to join Moxsie by giving us access to your address book information and allowing us to send emails on your behalf to your contacts. We do this because the more contacts you have on Moxsie, the better it works. For example, each of your contacts on Moxsie is connected to many other contacts that may not be connected to you. Thus, if Jane is a fan of your brand or boutique, Jane's friends can find out about you through her profile. Moxsie has also created special software for brands and stores that help you more easily manage your communications with your customers and fans on Moxsie. We want you to be able to take advantage of our services with full confidence that your email lists will not be shared with anyone, especially your competitors.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties.**

Moxsie is about sharing information with others — friends, designers, brands and boutiques in your network — this is how you can find out about new products, sales, and special events through your friends. The relationships among the people in your network allow us to recommend products and stores to you that your friends know, trust, and recommend. Our service, and the reliability of the recommendations that we provide to you, depend on trust relationships that you and your friends have established with the people, designers, and stores in your network. This is why you should never add a designer, person, or store that you do not like, know, or trust as a friend. Although Moxsie is about sharing information, we provide you with privacy settings that restrict other users from accessing your information. We allow you to choose the information you provide to friends and networks through Moxsie. Our network architecture and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your personal information. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. For example: 

• We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Moxsie, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Moxsie-specified purposes.

• We occasionally provide demonstration accounts that allow non-users a glimpse into the Moxsie world. Such accounts have only limited capabilities (e.g., messaging is disabled) and passwords are changed regularly to limit possible misuse.

• We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Moxsie service or using the Moxsie name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

• We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through sponsored groups or other on-site offers if and when this functionality is provided.

• We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other companies on Moxsie. You can tell when another company is involved in any store or service provided on Moxsie, and we may share customer information with that company in connection with your use of that store or service.

• If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Moxsie business, or individual business units owned by Moxsie, Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

When you use Moxsie, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, or other items, this information may become publicly available.

**Affiliated Business We Do Not Control:**

We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction. We will only share personal information that is necessary for the affiliate to complete the transaction. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do and they do not have the right to share or use personal information for any purpose other than for an authorized transaction.

• Personnel:

Our personnel (including, for the avoidance of doubt, consultants and/or contractors) may have access to user information while carrying out their duties in the normal course of our company business.

• Agents:

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. You hereby consent to our sharing of your personal information for the above purposes.

• Promotional Offers:

We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please notify us by e-mail at [unsubscribe@moxsie.com](mailto:unsubscribe@moxsie.com).

• Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Moxsie, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.

• Protection of Moxsie and Others:

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Moxsie, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Is Information About Me Secure?**

Your Moxsie account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

Only Moxsie employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

**What Information Can I Access?**

You can access your personal information on our website and correct, amend, or delete information that is inaccurate. To edit your personal information, go to your profile and click the edit button in the about section or go to the basic menu.

**What Choices Do I Have?**

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "What Personal Information About Users Does Moxsie Collect?" section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at [unsubscribe@moxsie.com](mailto:unsubscribe@moxsie.com). Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Moxsie website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

**Can Children Use Moxsie's Services?**

Moxsie does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Moxsie or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Moxsie. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@moxsie.com](mailto:info@moxsie.com). We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

**Conditions of Use**

If you decide to visit the Moxsie website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

**Third Party Websites**

Moxsie services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Moxsie website. These other websites are not under Moxsie control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Moxsie website are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Moxsie is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Moxsie may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Moxsie website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at the Moxsie website, please send a detailed message to [privacy@Moxsie.com](mailto:privacy@Moxsie.com). Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date of This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 20, 2008.

The best way to describe us is a cross between an online fashion magazine and a social network for fashion where designers can put their videos, collections, photographs, stories, link to stores that carry them or even sell direct online. We know how hard it is for smaller deginers to get noticed even when they are talented; so, Moxsie makes it easy for people to fined them and buy from them. We give talented designers a plataform where they can gain international exposure and connect and communicate with people that matter - be they boutiques, retailers, others brands, or Fashionistas that love their stuff.

We are continually scouting out the most cutting edge retailers, brands and designers around the world. We would be delighted to hear about brands you would like featured - just contact us.
